周六\N下午3点\N　\N
婚礼前27小时
距离巴尼和罗宾的婚礼还剩两天的时候
Two days before Barney and Robin's wedding,
他们的牧师挂了
their reverend passed away,
他们启动了寻找牧师大行动
and the search was on for a replacement.
哦天啊 又是那个
Oh, boy, it's the creepy,
黑暗教堂的肿泡眼牧师
bug-eyed minister from that culty church
老在追问我们是不是"至死纯洁"
who kept asking us if we're "Pure enough to die."
目前就数他最好了 我还是接了吧
He's our best lead. I should get this.
詹姆斯 除非你能找到个牧师
James, unless you have a minister,
不然我现在没空听你瞎扯
I don't want to hear it.
你说的牧师是 这种的吗
You mean, like this one?
几年前
A few years back,
巴尼他哥詹姆斯终于见到了他失散多年的父亲 山姆
Barney's brother James finally met his long-lost father, Sam,
他竟然还是一位牧师
who turned out to be a reverend.
现在我宣布 你们的小命有救了
I now pronounce your asses saved.
吉布斯牧师还不是唯一一个在那天出场的重量级人物
Reverend Gibbs wouldn't be the only VIP arrival that day.
爸爸
Dad!
巴尼 哦 真不敢相信你都要结婚了
Barney. Oh, I can't believe you're getting married.
你都长这么大了
You've grown up so fast.
不过话说回来 是我错过了你人生中的30年来着
Then again, I did miss about 30 years of your life.
我在登记处还给你们留了两份礼物哦
Did I mention we got you two things from your registry?
对了 一会儿能请你俩喝一杯吗
Hey, can we buy you guys a drink in a bit?
好啊 一会儿吧台见
Sure. We'll meet you at the bar.
哦 哇 快看
Oh. Whoa. Look.
我爸妈很多年没见过面了
My dad hasn't seen my mom in years,
自从我爸抛弃了我妈就再也没见过面了
not since he bailed on her.
哦天 资深离异家庭的小孩告诉你
Oh, man, take it from a fellow child of divorce,
这下可要乱套了
this could get real messy.
洛蕾塔 很高兴见到你
Loretta, good to see you.
我也是 杰瑞
You, too, Jerry.
喔
Wow.
谢天谢地 没什么狗血剧情上演
Yeah. Thank God, no drama.
他们深爱着彼此啊
They're in love!
我爸爸妈妈要复合啦
My mom and dad are getting back together again!
啊哦
Uh-oh.
老爸\N　　　  　　 老妈\N　　 　　 浪漫史\N　　  　　　　第九季  第十集\N
S09E10 Mom and Dad
翻译: @卟哒哒伽马 @小白是憎恶 @阿狸小H @毒舌的吊儿郎当\N @CIA_Kevin @肉鸭大魔王♥@晒小花
统筹+校对+后期+时间轴+压制\N硬汉难御肉鸭鸭 软妹易推小花花
HIMYM字幕组 倾情奉献
嘿 帮个小忙
Hey, quick favor.
我准备把这个给罗宾来着
I want to give this to Robin.
她是格雷茨基的脑残粉
Gretzky's her hero.
有时候她会在床上喊他的名字 我已经习惯了
She says his name sometimes in bed. I've accepted it.
在晚餐排练之前 你能不能 呃 帮我藏一下这个
Can you, uh, hide it for me till the rehearsal dinner?
伴郎出马你放心
The best man is on it.
太好了 现在要去让爸爸和妈妈复合啦
Great. Now I'm gonna go get my mom and dad back together.
他们完全坠入爱河了 是吧 超赞是不是
They're totally in love. I know. It's amazing.
今夜做梦都会笑
I'm walking on air.
我的家终于重新完整啦
My family's gonna be whole again!
我们要不要阻止他一下呢
Should we stop him or something?
伴郎我还是藏好格雷茨基吧
The best man is staying on the Gretzky thing.
* 我要大步前行五百里 *
Well, I would walk 500 miles and
* 还要继续跋涉五百多 *
I would walk 500 more
* 只为成就一次千里行 *
Just to be the man who walked a thousand miles
* 最后倒在你家门口 *
Then falls down at your door.
哈
Ha!
你说对了
You're right.
这破玩意还真心是洗脑神曲啊
That crap grows on you.
再来一遍不
Again?
来吧
Proclaim it!
这首歌的原唱是Proclaimers乐队
嘿 我刚才正躺在
Hey. So there I am,
天井下面那些脏兮兮湿乎乎的沙子上
lying in the wet, filthy sand under the patio,
思考人生的时候 我爸就撞见我妈了
just minding my own business, when my dad bumps into my mom,
然后他说 听着哦
and he says-- get this--
他跟她说"天气转好了 是吧"
he says to her, "Weather's improving, huh?"
简直了 他俩直接开干好了 对吧
It's like, why don't you just do it already? Huh?
巴尼 我知道你一直梦想有个完整的家
Barney, I know you've always dreamed of a reunited family,
但是... 杰瑞已经结婚了啊
but... Jerry's married.
那又怎样 婚姻不就是张纸吗 屁用都没有
So what? Marriage is just a meaningless piece of paper.
艾玛我真是个幸运的女孩
I'm a lucky gal.
亲爱的 这事儿没戏的
Sweetie, this just isn't gonna happen.
现在 我要你跟我保证
Now, please promise me
你没有在实施任何疯狂的计划
you haven't already put some crazy scheme in motion.
我没有在实施 任何 疯狂的计划
I haven't put some crazy scheme in motion.
你这停顿是啥意思
Why did you pause?
我没停啊
I didn't pause.
你停一会儿是啥意思
Why did you pause?!
楼梯湿滑
不 是坏掉了
对 楼梯坏掉了
啊 你好啊
Ah. Hey, there.
嗨
Hi.
巴尼发短信让我火速去找他
Barney texted me to meet him ASAP,
可是楼梯湿滑
but the stairs are wet.
不 是坏掉了
No, broken.
对 楼梯坏掉了
Yeah, the stairs are broken.
他也给我发了一样的短信
Yeah. I got the same text.
巴尼 杰瑞已经有老婆了
Barney, Jerry has a wife.
我的天啊 你把他老婆怎么了
Oh, God, what did you do to the wife?
好吧 我丈夫
So, my husband
偷偷跑去玩滑伞 然后现在让我去会合
snuck off to go parasailing, and he wants me to join him?
是的
Yes.
准备好享受这个
Who is ready to rock it
苏格兰二重唱模式
Scottish-identical- twin-brothers style?
500miles的原唱 Proclaimers 二人乐队组合
* 当我醒来 *
When I wake up
* 我就知道我一定 *
Yeah, I know I'm gonna be
* 我一定将在你身边醒过来 *
I'm gonna be the man who ends up next to you...
才发现啊 但愿他们不是对同一个妞唱的吧
Oh, man, I hope they're not singing to the same girl.
或者是对彼此唱的
Or to each other.
闭嘴 音乐什么的玩蛋去吧
Shut up! Music sucks!
苏格兰玩蛋去吧 你玩蛋吧
Scotland sucks! You suck!
专心开车 傻蛋
Just drive, pumpkin head.
嘿 你俩 别担心
Hey, guys, don't worry.
援兵马上就到
Help's on the way.
-哦 谢谢你 巴尼  -谢谢你 宝贝
-Oh! Thank you, Barney. -Thank you, honey.
与此同时呢
In the meantime,
我尽量让你俩舒服一些
I'll try to keep you two as comfortable as possible.
好吧 我们不要红酒
Well, we don't need wine.
也不要香槟好吧 我们需要援助
We don't need champagne, either. We need help!
这多不安全啊
This could be very unsafe!
安全来了
Oh.
我得说说他
I'll say something.
不 你操心操一辈子 这次我来说
No. You've had a whole lifetime of this. Let me.
哦
Oh.
巴尼 你是不是觉得
Barney, are you thinking
你能让我和你妈妈复合
you can get your mother and me back together?
可是我已经结婚了
Because I'm married.
我老婆就在楼上
My wife is right upstairs!
她才不在呢
No, she's not.
-怎么回事  -没怎么
-What's that? -Nothing!
我就是想以一场
I'm just trying to keep you refreshed
意外而又浮夸的电梯故障桥段 让你们重获新生
through this unexpected and flukish elevator malfunction!
再给你们来点水
Here's some water!
啊 不好
Ah... drat.
原谅巴尼笨手笨脚的
Clumsy hands much, Barney?
脱光光 然后把湿衣服送上来
Just disrobe and send up those wet clothes.
你们会挨冻的 等我去拿点草莓热能啫喱
You'll be cold, so I'll send down strawberry warming gel
一吹即热 谁用谁知道的东西 好孩子不要好奇
还有保温口罩来
and some cozy, zippered masks.
我的书法墨水
My calligraphy ink!
我是说 格雷茨基的照片
I mean, the Gretzky photo!
有个混蛋溜进我的房间
Some bastard snuck into my room
把我的墨水全洒在巴尼让我保管的
and spilled ink all over the Gretzky photo
格雷茨基的照片上了
I was holding for Barney.
大侦探莫斯比 重出江湖
Detective Mosby is on the case.
-哦 天啊 太可怕了  -我知道
-Oh, God, that's horrible. -I know.
那是给罗宾的礼物
It was a gift for Robin.
我是说
No, I mean,
哦天啊 太可怕了 大侦探莫斯比又来祸害人了
"Oh, God, that's horrible. Detective Mosby's the worst."
嗯 大侦探莫斯比
Mm, Detective Mosby is
破案时狂拽酷炫吊炸天
the case-crackingest private dick on the scene.
真的吗 比如那个都折腾八年了
Really? Like that case from eight years ago
都始终没破的案子 你怎么说
you still haven't cracked?
就在上周
还是到此为止吧
I'm callin' it.
妈的
Damn it!
我最伟大的失败啊
My greatest failure.
真相只有一个
I will solve this case.
把你给我那张大头照的时候
Now, there were three people nearby
只有三个人在附近
when Barney gave me that head shot:
功夫坏小子的比利•扎布卡
Karate Kid bad boy Billy Zabka,
贼眉鼠眼的服务员
a shifty-eyed bellhop,
还有罗宾的表兄 来自魁北克的
and Robin's cousin Claude from Quebec
颈椎犯病的克劳德
with the neck trouble.
对啊 毕竟你觉得这些鬼扯的阴谋论比
Right, 'cause an elaborate conspiracy is much more likely
你把照片放在没盖盖子的墨水瓶旁边更有可能了
than you leaving the photo next to an open ink bottle.
-多谢总结  -你连挖苦都侦测不到
-Thank you! -You can't even detect sarcasm!
你干嘛不试着弄好照片啊
Why don't you just try to fix the photo?
你就没有消字灵吗
Don't you have ink remover?
我当然有消字灵了
Of course I have ink remover.
我又不是那种邋遢朋克书法家
I'm not one of those sloppy, punk calligraphers
光说不练假把式的那种
who's in it for glory over craft.
我们得解决掉
No, we got to solve this!
现在问题就是
Now, the question is,
这三个犯罪嫌疑人中 谁最有理由陷害我
which of those three suspects had the most cause to frame me?
是被我替掉的那个前任伴郎吗
The one that I replaced as Barney's best man?
你给我等着 莫斯比
I'm coming for you, Mosby.
比利•扎布卡
Billy Zabka!
十万火急 我需要现采的英国薰衣草
Okay, real quick, I need fresh-cut English lavender,
一份莎士比亚的十四行诗第十八首
a copy of Shakespeare's 18th sonnet,
还有足够抹遍一个60岁女人全身的巧克力榛子酱
and enough Nutella to cover a 60-year-old woman.
好吧 你们居然逃跑了
Oh, great. You guys escaped.
营救成功哈
Got rescued!
你们还好吗
Are you okay?
受了点惊吓
A bit shaken up.
被困电梯很恐怖的
Being trapped in an elevator is scary.
不 是巴尼放下来一台电视
No, Barney lowered in a TV
播的声情并茂的70年代黄片太吓人了
showing some pretty graphic 1970s pornography.
还是有很多熟脸的哈
Still, a lot of familiar faces in there.
好吧 不只是脸
Well, not just faces.
我得找我老婆去
I'm gonna go find my wife.
看你干的好事
Nice job, bro.
自打妈妈怀上我以来
Mom was just about to get some action
这是她头一回准备采取点行动
for the first time since she conceived me.
巴尼 你得停手了
Barney, this has to stop.
你妄想症又发作了吧
You're being delusional.
妈妈才不会和杰瑞复合
Mom is not getting back together with Jerry.
因为她要和我爸爸复合啦
Because she's getting back together with my daddy!
我看出来你的猫腻了
I see what you're doing.
你把你爸带来不是为了给我俩证婚
You didn't bring your dad here to marry us.
而是想让他跟妈妈复合啊
You want him to get back together with Mom!
这太没天理了好吗
Which is completely insane, by the way.
呃 我爸爸单身 妈妈也是单身
Um, my dad's single, Mom's single.
而你爸婚姻幸福 儿女绕膝
Your dad's happily married with two kids.
哪个更能说得通
Which one makes more sense?
好吧 我同意 算平手
I agree. It's a tie.
我们该怎么办
What do we do?
你闪边
You back down
让我爸爸和妈妈重归于好
and let me get my mom and dad back together?
呃 不如你闪边
Um, how about you back down
让我爸爸和妈妈重归于好
and let me get my mom and dad back together?
我已经脑补出画面了
I can already picture it.
* 我们复合了呀 幸福欢乐多呀 *
We're reunited and we're going so strong
* 我老婆滑伞滑死了呀 而我看开了呀 *
My wife died parasailing and I've moved on
* 我们的巴尼宝贝陪伴左右呀 *
And now our Barney-boy will always be near
* 我要搬来住呀 一点也不怪呀 *
I'll come to live with you and it won't be weird
* 当然啦 小口耐 *
Of course not, Wuv-Wuv!
* 破镜重圆呀 永远相伴呀 *
Back together and forever we'll be
* 麻麻 *
Mom
* 拔拔 *
And Dad
* 和巴尼的三口之家 *
And Barney makes three
* 我们爱你 小家伙 *
We love you, champ!
* 而且我从结婚后也住在这里呀 *
And I'll live here, too, since we're married
* 我一点意见也没有呀 *
And I'm totally cool with it!
你精神病忘吃药了吧
That's completely insane.
事情会是这样的
This is how it's gonna be.
* 我们复合了呀 我好欢乐多呀 *
We're reunited and I'm feeling so glad
* 我比巴尼爸爸性感好多呀 *
I'm so much sexier than Barney's dad
* 破镜又重圆呀 生活回正轨呀 *
Back together, now our life's right on track
* 但她背着你爸 偷偷上我爸呀 *
But she's banging my dad behind your dad's back
* 你去上班时 我就在她身后呀 *
When you're at work, I'm all over her rack
* 他乱说 *
That's not true
* 才没有 *
Yes, it is
* 不好笑 *
That's not funny
* 妈妈 插播一下 *
Mom, break the news
* 好呀 我们像小兔 尽情啪啪啪 *
Okay, we're screwin' like bunnies
* 我要宰了你 *
I'll kick your ass
* 你来呀你来呀 *
I'd like to see you try
* 打赢的肯定是我爸 *
Well, my dad would win in a fight
No, my dad would win in a fight
* -才不会  -就是会 *
-No -Yeah
* 打赢的一定是我爸 *
My dad would win in a fight
才不是 打赢的肯定是我爸 哼哼
No, my dad would win in a fight! Nuh-uh!
别打啦
Don't fight!
我要嫁进这家门啊
I'm marrying into this family.
-你个傻蛋  -我才不停
-You stupid! -I won't stop.
滑伞的地方到底在哪啊
Where the heck is this parasailing place?
你等一下
You know what?
我得 我得给杰瑞打个电话
I'm gonna... I'm gonna call Jerry.
奇了怪了
Oh, that's weird.
我一点信号都收不到了
I just lost cell reception.
是吗
Yes.
真是奇怪呢
Weird.
这个旅馆里美画连连啊
Lot of pretty paintings in this hotel.
而且一个个裱得也好看
I like how they've been... framed.
frame双关裱和陷害
我也注意到了那些古色古香的
I've noticed the vintage, antique,
镀金维多利亚风格的画框
gilded Victorian frames, too.
我又不瞎 你想说什么
I'm not blind... but what are you getting at?
你跟我装什么二愣子呢
You know damn well what I'm getting at!
你嫉妒我又做回了伴郎
You're jealous I got the Best Mansmanship back,
所以你想出毒计 毁了那签名照片
so you destroyed that photo as part of some diabolical scheme
就是为了让我难堪
to make me look bad.
你肯定还准备了另一张韦恩•格雷茨基的照片
I bet you even found some other photo of Wayne Gretzky
就是为了关键时刻出来力挽狂澜对不对
so you could swoop in and save the day.
-你有病吧你  -有吗
-You're insane. -Am I?
-你就是  -是吗  -绝对是
-Yeah. -Am I? - Yeah.
下午三点十五的时候你在哪
Where were you today at 3:15 p.M.?
就在这里享受了
Right here getting a massage.
六十分钟的深层组织按摩
Rocked a 60-minute deep tish.
现在要是没什么事 大侦探
Now if you'll excuse me, Detective,
我就吃菠萝去了
I think I'll go have some pineapple.
你怎么知道菠萝那事的
How do you know about that?
地球人都知道啊
Everybody knows about that!
-打扰一下  -什么事
-Excuse me? -Mm?
是你毁了那张照片 对不对
You destroyed that photo, didn't you?
不是我干的
No, I didn't.
别装了 我向领班投诉你了
Admit it! I complained about you
你就想报复我
to the bell captain, so you got your revenge.
你向领班投诉我了吗
You complained about me?
没有
No.
慢点走 克劳德
So, Claude...
我听说你是蒙特利尔加拿大人队的球迷
I see that you're a Montreal Canadiens fan.
也就是说你讨厌埃德蒙顿油工队
Which means you hate the Edmonton Oilers,
这也解释了你为什么会毁了韦恩•格雷茨基的大头照
which is why you destroyed the Wayne Gretzky head shot!
我指控你
J'accuse!
你这叫毫无根据
C'est ridicule!
要是毫无根据的话
If it's so ridicule,
那你怎么解释你的手
how do you explain this?
看起来我抓到了... 你沾满墨水的双手
Ah, seems like I've caught you...midnight blue-handed.
你说这个啊
Oh, these. Yeah.
当时我在海边
I-I was out by the water when...
一个老年塔法里人驾驶着滑翔机
an elderly R-Rastafarian hang glider...
掉到了沙滩上的一只乌贼上
he-he crash onto a beached squid,
我过去救人的时候被墨汁溅上了
which squirted ink when I ran in to help.
就这个破理由你还指望我信你吗
You really expect me to believe that?
证据确凿
Story checks out.
错怪你了 克劳德
Sorry, Claude.
没关系
De rien.
我没搞明白
I don't get it.
本来好好的
We were bonding.
我什么都没做错好吗
I can't think of anything I did wrong!
好吧 做了那么几件错事
Okay, I did a few things wrong.
我最后一次重申
For the last time,
我没把你买的那些橙子放在车顶
I did not leave the bag of oranges you bought on the roof!
别再超速了啊
No more breaking the speed limit. And, uh,
多谢提醒我她跑到了67英里
thanks for flagging me down and telling me she was going 67.
美国高速限速65英里
只是做个守法公民罢了 警官
Just following the rules, Officer.
对了 她还没系安全带
Oh. She's also not wearing her seat belt.
那个词不是你能用的
You are not allowed to use that word!
只有我们才能用
Only we're allowed to use that word!
对不起
I am so sorry.
我以后再也不敢叫你或别人
I will never call you or anyone else a...
星际脑残粉了
Trekkie again.
但是我道过歉你也接受了
But I apologized and you accepted.
我还买了橙子赔给你
I even bought you more oranges.
我气的不是你 明白了吗
Look, it wasn't you, okay?
宝贝 我知道你在模拟联合国的发言很重要
Baby, I know your speech at the Model U.N. Is a big deal,
但是我不知道我赶不赶得及了
but I'm just not sure I'll make it in time.
我在努力赶路
I'm trying.
你知道吗
You know what?
你直接别来算了
Don't bother coming.
也就是说你当时在机场说的是真的了
So, back at the airport, that story was true?
你有个女儿吗
You have a daughter?
她跟她爸过
She lives with her dad.
而且因为我老是出差 总是错过很多
And since I travel for work, I miss a lot of stuff.
我努力工作也是为了让她过上好日子
I only work as hard as I do to provide for her.
孩子不认逻辑
But kids, they don't understand logic.
孩子只认有谁陪伴
Kids understand who shows up.
这就是为什么她爸爸是她的英雄
That's why her dad's her hero...
而我却被挂电话
and I get hung up on.
去看你女儿的演讲吧
Go see your daughter's speech.
只要你出现 一切都会被原谅的
If you show up, all will be forgiven.
别管这事儿了
Just drop it.
直接开回我家吧
And drop me at home.
然后赶快去你那场婚礼
Then head out to your wedding.
讨论结束
End of discussion.
巴尼 哪怕你的计划能成功
Barney, even if your plan worked,
你也毁了你爸爸的婚姻啊
you'd be destroying your dad's marriage.
好吧 你说的有那么一点道理
Okay, you may have a point.
我能提个建议吗
Can I suggest something?
休战吧
Truce?
我们都同意放下这件事如何
We both agree to drop this.
同意
Agreed.
对了 我新换了一瓶
Hey, I got a replacement bottle
-30年陈的格伦•麦肯纳  -好
-of 30-year Glen McKenna. -Okay.
听着 就算妈妈再也没有跟
Look, even if Mom never gets back together
我们俩的爸爸之一复合 我们仍然是兄弟
with either one of our dads, we're still brothers.
这可不是比赛
It's not a competition.
我赢啦
I win!
把你的臭手从我妈身上拿下来
Get your damn hands off my mom!
把你的臭手放到我妈身上去
Get your damn hands on my mom!
一只放上去一只拿下来吗
One on, one off?
这到底怎么回事
What the hell is going on here?
几年前 在你们哥俩找到山姆之后
After you boys tracked Sam down a few years back,
我们联系上了 我们又成为了朋友
we got in touch. We became friends again,
-开始一起玩  -然后某一天
-started hanging out. -And then one day,
她从洛蕾塔变成了...
she went from being Loretta to being...
洛♀蕾♀塔
Lo-ret-ta.
我们想等等再告诉你们
We wanted to wait to tell you
因为时间还不长
because it's still new,
但一旦山姆来主持婚礼仪式
but it was inevitable you'd find out
你们肯定会发现这事的
once Sam came to perform the ceremony.
这是你俩的亲密用语吗
Is that what you two call it?
"主持婚礼仪式"
"Performing the ceremony"?
不 山姆明天会为你证婚啊 亲爱的
Oh, Sam's marrying you tomorrow, dear.
哦对 多谢你了 牧师大人
Right. Thank you, Reverend.
听着 你们可以好好的接受这件事吗
Look, is there any way you guys can be all right with this?
我当然可以啦
Of course I am!
巴尼呢
Barney?
我知道我今天一直不正常 但...
I know I've been acting crazy today, but...
我只有一个真正想问的问题 妈妈
I just have one real question, Mom,
我希望得到诚实的回答
and I want an honest answer.
有没有这样一刻
Is there a scenario--
听我说完
and hear me out--
你曾经考虑过
where you might consider
跟我们俩的爸爸们一起来个三人行呢
doing kind of a three-way deal with both of our dads?
-天哪 你到底什么毛病  -喂 老弟 说什么呢
-God! What is wrong with you?! -Oh, dude, come on!
我就知道会这样
That's what I thought!
是时候承认了 泰德
It's time to admit it, Ted.
是你自己弄洒了墨水 根本就没有什么阴谋
You spilled the ink. There's no conspiracy.
我想也是吧
I guess you're right.
我是说 只剩下最后一个
I mean, the only other person
看到巴尼给我那张照片的人了...
who saw Barney give me that photo...
就是你
was you.
嘿 白痴
Hey. Idiot.
在你忙着玩侦探游戏的时候
While you've been playing detective,
我一直在帮你收拾烂摊子
I've been cleaning up your mess.
看 消字灵很有效呢
Look, the ink remover works.
我去把这个弄好
I'm gonna finish this.
你去向巴尼坦白
You come clean to Barney.
好吧
Okay.
她已经消失一整天了
She's been missing all day,
而且我在我床上找到一张疑似自杀留言的东西
a-and I found what appears to be a-a suicide note on my bed.
但语气并不像她
But it doesn't really sound like her.
"我要杀了我...等一下...自己"
"I'm going to kill my-- wait for it-- self."
扎布卡先生还好吗
Is everything okay with Mr. Zabka?
等等 等一下 你为什么认为那是比利•扎布卡
Wait. W-Wait. Why do you think that's Billy Zabka?
看到没
See?
是大堂那个男人做的这个按摩
The man from the lobby got this massage.
一位年轻一些的先生作为礼物送他的
A younger gentleman bought it for him as a gift.
还帮他签名了
He even signed his name for him.
就在这儿
Right here.
我告诉你们...
I'm telling all y'all...
这是扎布卡破坏
it's Zabka-tage.
原词为sabotage 蓄意破坏
Sabotage by Beastie Boy
星际迷航主题曲
* 我已忍无可忍 我知道你掌控了全局 *
I can't stand it, I know you planned it
* 我这就要把一切澄清 整个局中局 *
I'm gonna set it straight, this Watergate
* 我在里面已经不能忍受其中的韵律 *
I can't stand rocking when I'm in here
* 因为你的水晶球并不像你说的那样清澈透明 *
'Cause your crystal ball ain't so crystal clear
* 当你靠着椅子思考为什么的时候 *
So while you sit back and wonder why
* 我已芒刺在手 *
I got this ... thorn in my side
莉莉在这个周末的第二次虎扑
Lily's second tackle of the weekend.
毁灭吧
Sabotage.
醒一醒吧 我们到了
Wakey, wakey.
等等 这不是...
Wait, this isn't...
这是你女儿的学校
It's your daughter's school.
你需要进去
You need to go in.
她说让我不要来了
She asked me not to come, Marshall.
这完全讲不通啊
This doesn't make any sense.
孩子不认逻辑
Kids don't understand logic.
孩子只认有谁陪伴
Kids understand who shows up.
人们常说 孩子就是未来
People say children are the future.
我说...
I say...
石油才是未来
oil is the future!
少听点那些胆小如鼠娘们儿唧唧的环保主义者的屁话
Don't listen to these gutless environmental sissies!
-这才是我姑娘  -勘探海洋
-That's my baby. -Drill in the oceans!
-谢谢你  -勘探湿地
-Thank you. -Drill in the wetlands!
-傻冒  -勘探国家公园
-Pumpkin head. -Drill in the national parks!
不客气
You're welcome.
宝贝 快来钻 宝贝 快来钻
Drill, baby, drill! Drill, baby, drill!
-宝贝 快来钻  -我们该走了
-Drill, baby, drill! -We should go.
宝贝 快来钻 宝贝 快来钻
Drill, baby, drill! Drill, baby, drill!
宝贝 快来钻
Drill, baby, drill!
你都说了
You said it was nuts
我让我的父母重归于好这个想法很疯狂
to think that my mom and dad would get back together.
但是詹姆斯和我想得一样
But that's what happened for James.
我从五岁开始就一直幻想着
I've been dreaming of that since I was five.
当然除了这个以外 还想要一个我自己能操控的死星
Well, that and my own operational Death Star.
星球大战中黑武士毁灭星球的空间站
但最主要还是他们重归于好
But mostly them getting back together.
为什么詹姆斯的想法实现了 我却没有
Why does James get it and I don't?
嗯 你想想
Well, think about it.
你有了我 你爸爸有了谢丽尔
You have me, your dad has Cheryl...
所以 综上所述
"So to summarize:
我死定了
"I'm super dead,
你应该和洛蕾塔好好啪啪啪
"You should totally bone Loretta,
我从未爱过你 谢丽尔
"And I never loved you, Cheryl,"
名字还拼错了
which is misspelled.
...詹姆斯刚刚离婚
...but James is going through a divorce.
他刚刚失去了家庭
He just lost his family.
我知道你一直有这个梦想 但是...
I-I know you've been dreaming of this, but...
也许 他比你更需要"合家欢"里面的情节
maybe he needs "Mom and Dad" More than you.
所以 比利 你真的觉得你能瞒天过海吗
So, Billy, did you really think you could get away with it?
实话说 我是这么想的
Actually, I did.
-啊  -我本来想
-Ah. I was gonna
把这个给巴尼的
give this to Barney
然后说我开了一个小时的车
and say I'd driven an hour away
在一个卖签名照的人手里买了一个新的
to get a replacement from an autograph dealer.
首先 我需要不在场证明
First, I needed an alibi.
所以我让巴尼的爸爸去做按摩
So I got Barney's dad a massage
但是我签的是自己的名字
but signed in my name.
接下来我把格雷茨基的大头照换成我
Then I switched the Gretzky head shot with one of myself.
我后备箱里常年放着
I always travel with 2,000 of those handsome devils
两千多张我英俊的小恶魔照片
in the trunk of my car.
我有无数个问题要问你 但是首先...
I have so many questions for you, but first...
你为什么把两千多张你的大头照放在你车里
you keep 2,000 head shots of yourself in your trunk?
因为没人要啊 他们只想要
No one ever wants them! They only want
好人的签名照
the "Good guy's" Autograph!
在80年代 我在每部电影里都是反面人物
In the '80s, I was the bad guy in every movie.
你知道我人生是什么样子的吗
Do you know what my life has been like?
每次首映 当我出现的时候...
Every premiere, when I came on-screen...
但我在生活中不是坏人啊
I wasn't a bad guy in real life,
只是一个很不错的演员啊
just a kick-ass actor.
但是没人懂我...
No one got that.
不管我在哪都有人这么做
It happened everywhere I went.
也不知道为什么 他们总有爆米花在他们手里
Somehow, people always had popcorn.
功夫小子中的经典桥段
二十五年了 我都在被人踢爆蛋蛋
25 years of getting crane-kicked in the nuts,
直到巴尼•斯丁森给了我人生中最光彩夺目的一天
until Barney Stinson gave me the best moment of my life.
嘿 嘿 泰德那边出了一点问题 所以...
Hey. Hey, some issues just came up with Ted, so...
你愿意当我的伴郎吗
will you be my best man?
-当然  -谢谢
-Sure. -Thanks.
-喂  -妈
-Hello? -Mom?
别 别 听着 听
No, no, listen, listen.
我刚成了某人的伴郎
I just became somebody's best man.
今年感恩节你可以来了
You can come to Thanksgiving this year!
在巴尼•斯丁森眼中 我不是坏人
To Barney Stinson, I wasn't a bad guy.
在巴尼•斯丁森眼中 我是他的伴郎
To Barney Stinson, I was the best man.
我就想着要是泰德再搞砸一次 我就又有机会了
I thought if Ted screwed up again, I'd have another shot.
想必 我这回真的是个坏人了
But I guess this time I really was the bad guy.
怎么了 泰德 什么事情这么紧急
Hey, Ted, what's so urgent?
有些事情我要告诉你
I have something to tell you.
我把格雷茨基的大头照毁了
I destroyed that Gretzky head shot
我修复不了 比利力挽狂澜
and I couldn't fix it. Billy saved the day
跑到附近的卖签名照的地方买了个新的
by getting a new one from an autograph dealer nearby.
一小时车程呢
A-An hour away.
对对 一小时 淡定点
An hour away. Just be cool.
太棒了 谢谢你 比利
Awesome. Thanks, Billy!
还有 泰德
And, Ted...
我很高兴你说了实话
I really appreciate that you told the truth.
-痛  -去你的
-Ow -Psych!
比利牛人 泰德衰人
Billy rules, Ted drools,
斯丁森闪人
Stinson out.
没事啦 莫斯比
You're all right, Mosby.
而就是这百年难见的神奇周末
And for an all too rare moment that weekend,
竟然一切安好
everything was all right.
呃 巴尼
Um, Barney?
你就是这样支持我们的吗
Is this your way of saying you're supporting us?
是的 快上吧
Yes! Go for it.
达到爱的巅峰吧
Consummate your love!
谢谢了 兄弟
Thanks, bro.
但这很奇怪啊
But this is super weird.
各种奇怪
Super weird.
我们快到了吗
Are we almost there?
很快就到了
Almost there.
还我老婆 你个贱人
Give me back my wife, you son of a bitch!
HIMYM字幕组 谢谢观看
《老爸老妈浪漫史》下集预告
On the next episode of How I Met Your Mother
在《老爸老妈浪漫史》劲爆最终季上
On How I met Your Mother's big final season
将无缘无故迎来一场饕餮盛宴
comes a tasty new show all in line for no reason.
现在登场的是怒放的巴尼 狩猎着柔美的宝贝们
Here's some Barney in bloom, hunting babes soft and pretty.
-正如他自拟的头衔那样 -纽约城的玩家之王
-as he clinches the title: -Player King of New York City.
快加入我们吧 亲爱的观众
So join us dear viewer.
地址你懂的
You know the address.
下周一全新亮相 尽在CBS
It's all new next Monday and on CBS.
北京时间下周二 HIMYM字幕组与您共同期待